Southern Tenant Farmers Union Photographs 5859 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Tenant Farmers Union Photographs
1937-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Tenant Farmers' Union
5859 P
1.11 cubic feet
1.1 linear ft.
Photographs, negatives, contact sheets.
7944661
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 14, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 22, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5204: Southern Tenant Farmers Union. Speeches and Interviews. 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records 5859: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Research Files 6252 MB: Brian McNeill, Collector. Southern Tenant Farmers Union. Memorabilia.
Southern Tenant Farmers' Union
7944661
- Block, Raphael - Home & Clipping - 1937 (Land Lord of Myrtle & Ben Lawrence) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1 photograph
- Block, Raphael - Home - 1937 - negative (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Delta Cooperative - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  12 photographs
- Delta Cooperative - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  11 photographs
- Dyess Colony, 1937 (Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  6 photographs
- Family - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  18 photographs
- Family - 1937 - Negatives (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fieldwork - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  22 photographs
- Fieldwork - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  13 photographs
- Homes - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  15 photographs
- Lawrence, Myrtle & Ben - 1937 - Home (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Letter from Myrtle Lawrence - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  3 photographs
- Letter from Myrtle Lawrence - 1937 (negative) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Lula, Miss 1937 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- McKinney, E.B. (STFU Vice-President) 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Photos - 1937 -- (Outdoor Union meetings, Parkers, Arkansas) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Mitchell, H.L. (Executive Secretary - Later- President) STFU - 1937 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  8 photographs
- Road Signs (On the way to Lawrence's house) Arkansas, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  5 photographs
- Southern Tenant Farmers Union - Meeting - Parkin, Arkansas -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  31 photographs
- Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Meeting - Parkin, Arkansas -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  9 photographs
- Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Meeting - Parkin, Arkansas -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  29 photographs
- Southern Tenant Farmers' Union - Leaders & Activities -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Identifications of Contact Sheets and Individuals - 1937 -- (Xeroxes) (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Identifications of Individuals (Originals) -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Contact Sheet - Dyess Colony; In book Union Meeting -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Roll #1
- Contact Sheet - STFU Meeting - Parkin, Arkansas -- 1937 (negatives) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Roll #2
- Contact Sheets - STFU meeting - Parkin, Arkansas - 1937; Also photos of Mitchell, H.L. (and negatives) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  roll #3
- Contact Sheets - Homes, Fieldwork and Family - 1937 (negatives) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  roll #4
- Contact Sheets - Mitchell, Griffin, Blackstone, Farm Equipment, Road Signs -- 1937 (negatives) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  roll #5
- Delta Cooperative - 1937 - Contact Sheets & Negatives (Box 2, Folder 30)
  roll #6
- Lawrence, Ben & Delta Cooperative; Lawrence, Myrtle with Kester Family Dinner Photos -- Contact Sheets/negatives, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  roll #7
- Delta Cooperative - 1937 -- Contact Sheets & negatives (Box 2, Folder 32)
  roll #8
- Fieldwork; Lawrence's 1937 Home, Family - 1937 -- Contact Sheets/negatives (Box 2, Folder 33)
  roll #9
- STFU Meeting, Parkin, Arkansas - 1937 -- Contact Sheet (Box 2, Folder 34)
  roll #10
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous -- 1937 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous - 1937 -- Xeroxes -- Contact Sheets (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous -- 1937 -- Xeroxes - Contact Sheets (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous - 1937 -- Originals -- Contact Sheets (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous - 1937 - Originals - Contact Sheets (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Arkansas - Cherry Valley, Forest City - 08/1982 -- (Contact Sheets, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Arkansas, Colt -- 08/1982 (Contact Sheets, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Arkansas, Colt -- 08/1982 (Contact Sheets, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Arkansas: Colt, Dyess, Parkin -- 08/1982 (Contact Sheets & negatives) (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Arkansas - Colt, Parkin, and Wynne - 08/1982 (Contact Sheets, negatives) (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Arkansas: Colt, Wynne - 08/1982 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Arkansas: Parkin - 08/1982 (Contact Sheets) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  2 photographs
- Arkansas: Cherry Valley, Forest City / Tennessee: Memphis (Project Sharecropper) -- 08/1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  file no. 1 -- 10 photographs
- Arkansas: Dyess, Parkin / Tennessee: Memphis -- 08/1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  file no. 4 -- 2 photographs
- Florida, Tampa - 198(1)? - Family (Box 3, Folder 4)
  14 photographs
- Florida: Tampa - 1982 - LBI (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Florida: Tampa - 1982 -- LBII (Box 3, Folder 6)
  10 photographs
- Florida: Tampa - 1982 - LBIII (Box 3, Folder 7)
  7 photographs
- Miscellaneous Photos - 1980's (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Misc. - 08/1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Tennessee, Memphis - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- DeWitt Historical Society Exhibit (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 2 photographs sorted out of the 'misc. photos' box that had been stored over the mapcase (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Oversize photos